<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Single Player on Udayan Senapati</title>
    <link>https://usenapati.github.io/tags/single-player/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Single Player on Udayan Senapati</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:21:10 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://usenapati.github.io/tags/single-player/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Galaga3D</title>
      <link>https://usenapati.github.io/games/galaga3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:21:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usenapati.github.io/games/galaga3d/</guid>
      <description>Galaga3D is a 3D Space Shooter Game based off of the original Galaga arcade game. Fight and evade countless waves of enemies using your blasters or lasers and try to beat your own high scores.
The game was developed with a team of three during the VGDC 2022 Spring Jam, where the theme was recycle. The game was developed using Unity and all game models were created using Blender.
The team included:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLONE WARS Tabletop Tower Defense</title>
      <link>https://usenapati.github.io/games/clonewars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usenapati.github.io/games/clonewars/</guid>
      <description>CLONE WARS is a AR Tower Defense Game based in the Star Wars universe. The Player scans a 3D space, then they can add towers and enemy spawners. Each round, the towers must defend the player’s ship from waves of enemies. The player can use points earned each round to buy more towers.
The game was originally a friend&amp;rsquo;s school project that grew into a personal project with a team of four.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nekomancer</title>
      <link>https://usenapati.github.io/games/nekomancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usenapati.github.io/games/nekomancer/</guid>
      <description>Nekomancer is a 3D platformer whre you play as a cat, who was raised from the dead, and now have to search for ingredients to make a cure for your zombification. Throughout the game, you collect ingredients to make potions. The potions grant different powers, including super speed, static cling, or elasticity.
Nekomancer was developed with a team in a eight during the Red Storm and VGDC @ NCSU Game Jam, where the theme was zombie cats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transfusion</title>
      <link>https://usenapati.github.io/games/transfusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 14:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usenapati.github.io/games/transfusion/</guid>
      <description>Transfusion is a VR sword-fighting action game about violence. It takes place in a brutal alien world inspired by a fusion of Aztec and Roman cultures. You play as a prisoner who has to earn their freedom by slaying wave after wave of enemies in gladiatorial combat, as well as utilizing the gifts of a bloodthirsty deity. Along the way, you uncover a story that explores themes of violence, identity and sacrifice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
