<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows on Udayan Senapati</title>
    <link>https://usenapati.github.io/tags/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows on Udayan Senapati</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:21:10 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://usenapati.github.io/tags/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Galaga3D</title>
      <link>https://usenapati.github.io/games/galaga3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:21:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usenapati.github.io/games/galaga3d/</guid>
      <description>Galaga3D is a 3D Space Shooter Game based off of the original Galaga arcade game. Fight and evade countless waves of enemies using your blasters or lasers and try to beat your own high scores.
The game was developed with a team of three during the VGDC 2022 Spring Jam, where the theme was recycle. The game was developed using Unity and all game models were created using Blender.
The team included:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2D C&#43;&#43; Game Engine</title>
      <link>https://usenapati.github.io/games/2dgameengine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usenapati.github.io/games/2dgameengine/</guid>
      <description>The C++ Game Engine (Name TBD) was created for my Game Engine Foundations course. This was a solo project that was developed throughout my semester with multiple iterations. Each iteration added new features and systems related to topics such as Collision Detection, Input Handling, Multithreading, Networking, Time Scale, Game-Object Models, Event Management, and Scripting. Over the course of the class, I developed two games using the engine: a multiplayer side-scroller platformer and a top-down survival game with enemy AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nekomancer</title>
      <link>https://usenapati.github.io/games/nekomancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usenapati.github.io/games/nekomancer/</guid>
      <description>Nekomancer is a 3D platformer whre you play as a cat, who was raised from the dead, and now have to search for ingredients to make a cure for your zombification. Throughout the game, you collect ingredients to make potions. The potions grant different powers, including super speed, static cling, or elasticity.
Nekomancer was developed with a team in a eight during the Red Storm and VGDC @ NCSU Game Jam, where the theme was zombie cats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mecha Mania</title>
      <link>https://usenapati.github.io/games/mechamania/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 17:10:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usenapati.github.io/games/mechamania/</guid>
      <description>Mecha Mania is a multiplayer first-person shooter inspired by Titanfall 2 and the Gundam franchise. The game is being developed in Unreal Engine 5 and will be available for Windows. Compete in a 3v3 team deathmatch where you must gather mech parts and obliterate the enemy team with your completed mech. Throughout the arena, you&amp;rsquo;ll have an arsenal of weapons and tools to help you stop the enemy team. Use your movement abilities, including wallrunning, sliding, and climbing, to traverse your environment and outmaneuver your enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transfusion</title>
      <link>https://usenapati.github.io/games/transfusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 14:44:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://usenapati.github.io/games/transfusion/</guid>
      <description>Transfusion is a VR sword-fighting action game about violence. It takes place in a brutal alien world inspired by a fusion of Aztec and Roman cultures. You play as a prisoner who has to earn their freedom by slaying wave after wave of enemies in gladiatorial combat, as well as utilizing the gifts of a bloodthirsty deity. Along the way, you uncover a story that explores themes of violence, identity and sacrifice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
